放开我
Get the hell off me!
起来 站好
Get up! Stand up!
站好 站好 别打了
Stand up. Stand up. Stand up. Come on!
放开我
Let go of me!
站好
Stand up! Hey!
我不管你怎么做
I don't care how you do it.
有必要可以发全舰通告
Issue a shipwide announcement if you have to.
- 找到他  - 遵命 大副
- Just find him.  - Aye, Master Chief.
长官来了
Officer on deck.
散了
As you were.
跟我来 军士长
With me, Chief.
我知道今早在新兵食堂出了点状况
I understand we had a situation in the Enlisted Galley this morning.
我相信他们只是小打小闹
I'm sure they were just letting off a little steam, sir.
船员们可能对拓展任务有点小紧张
The crew's probably a little stressed from the extended mission.
你我都知道没有借口 大副
Oh, you and I both know that's no excuse, Master Chief.
如果他们现在紧张了 那到了战场上会是什么鬼样子
If they're stressed now, what the hell are they going to be like in a combat situation?
我要看下NCIS的报告
I want to read the NCIS report.
我也要看下
That makes two of us, sir.
我们还是没找到舰上特别探员
We still can't find the Special Agent Afloat.
找到他
Find him.
请NCIS海上特别探员Niles速联系安保长官
Would NCIS Special Agent Afloat Niles please contact the watch commander?
== 海军罪案调查处：洛杉矶 第四季第10集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译:忘枫 小太爷 顾顾 BG-Sandman ==
== 校对: BG-Sandman 瑶小瑶 忘枫 后期&封装:忘枫 ==
本字幕仅用于学习交流之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
套不上
I don't get it.
Hetty 我可以解释
Hetty, I-I can explain. Uh...
实际上 这是我的错
Actually, no, this is my fault.
我叫Eric帮我做"给孩子们玩具"的活动
I asked Eric to help me out with the Toys for Tots program
我是给海军陆战队做的
I'm doing for the Marine Corps, and, well,
我觉得孩子看着我们装扮下会很好玩
I thought it would be fun for the kids if we were dressed up.
没错 听起来棒极了
Yes. It sounds wonderful.
但我恐怕这得等等
But I'm afraid it'll have to wait.
我们失去了一个自己人
We've lost one of our own.
集合队伍
Rally the troops.
Beale先生
Mr. Beale?
你有个精灵头型
You have, um, elf head.
不到一周就圣诞节了
So, Christmas is less than a week away.
要是幸运的话 我们还可以休假几天
One of the very few holidays we get off, if we're lucky.
- 你有啥计划吗  -没
- And you have no plans?  - Nope.
- 确定吗  - 是的
- Swear?  - Yes.
- 好极了  - 你别想了
- Perfect.  - No.
很好
Yes!
不 你别想了 我已经决定不做任何事
No, no, nono, because I have chosen not to do anything.
这不是默认情况
It was not by default.
我做了个很清醒的决定 圣诞节不做任何事
I have made a conscious choice not to do anything on Christmas.
也就是变身为有30只猫的疯婆子第一步
Also known as step one to become the crazy lady with 30 cats.
Kensi 好好考虑下 太浩湖
Kensi, think about this. Lake Tahoe.
滑进滑出的小屋 六尺深的瑞雪
Ski-in, ski-out cabin. Six feet of fresh powder.
白天滑雪 夜晚围绕在篝火边
Snowboarding during day, roaring fire at night.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
你是不是太差劲了
Do you suck?
说啥
Excuse me?
滑雪技术很差
At snowboarding?
要知道这需要很高的协调性
just know it takes a lot of coordination.
我们可以给你要个平底雪橇
Maybe we could get you, like, a toboggan.
我会滑雪
I can snowboard.
- 他们有初学者滑雪道  - 我才不需要呢
- They have a bunny hill.  - I don't need a bunny hill.
那你怕什么
What are you so afraid of?
我可什么都不怕
I'm not afraid of anything.
我随时随地都能虐爆你
I could kick your ass anytime, anywhere.
姐可是双黑道级别的
This...double-black-diamond rated.
我从不怀疑你是双黑道级别的
There is no doubt in my mind that that is double-black-diamond rated.
还有 我跟我妈妈说了圣诞节陪她
Plus, I told my mom I'd spend Christmas with her.
那么叫她也来吧
Well, then, she should come.
那可是三室一厅的小屋
It's a three-bedroom cabin.
两间是连通的
Two of which are connected.
你别想了
Don't even think about it.
- 给你妈妈  - 哟
- For your mom.  - Ew!
和你的 你俩可以并房
And you, so you guys could have adjoining rooms.
你想啥呢
What are you thinking?
没啥
Nothing.
我确信你想歪了
I bet you were.
可能给我妈妈一个假期也不错
It might actually be nice to give my mom a little vacation.
还有什么能比得上白色圣诞节呢
And what's better than a white Christmas?
就我们仨 出去逛逛
Just the three of us, hanging out...
喝喝热饮
sipping hot cocoa,
看雪从柏树上飘落
watching the snow fall on the cedars.
- 去泡温泉  - 哦
- From the hot tub.  - Oh!
- 你非要这么意淫  - 咋了
- You had to go there.  - What?
她是只冷透的狐狸
She's a stone-cold fox.
- 你毁了假期  - 我没有
- You ruined it!  - I didn't.
我使它更美好了 不是吗 Nell
I made it better. Didn't I, Nell?
Hetty要你们去行动中心
Hetty needs you guys up in Ops.
好极了
Great.
Hetty要你们去行动中心
Hetty needs you guys up in Ops.
好的 我们马上去
Okay, we'll be right there.
我能帮上什么忙吗
Can I help you with something?
如果你知道他在找什么或是放哪了就能帮上忙
You could, if he knew what he was looking for or where he put it.
我可不想再经历一遍去年的小马玩偶的事
I didn't want to go through that whole Parker Pony thing like I did last year,
所以我六月就问我女儿圣诞节想要啥
so I asked my daughter what she wanted for Christmas in June,
然后马上出门就买好了
and then I went out to buy it right away.
为了不让她发现 他藏得很深
He hid it so she wouldn't find it.
当然了 我们都知道记忆是先衰老的
Of course, as we know, the memory is the first to go.
我觉得好像与哈利波特有关
I think it had something to do with Harry Potter.
魔杖吗
A wand?
不是
No.
一只猫头鹰呢
How about an owl?
- 不是  - 不是吗
- No.  - No?
分院帽吗
A sorting hat?
啥
A what?
扫帚呢
A broom?
你根本就帮不上忙
You're not helping.
我也没想帮啊
Eh, I'm not really trying.
Eric 我们看的是谁
Who we looking at, Eric?
Jason Niles 美国范布伦号航母上的NCIS驻舰特别探员
Jason Niles was the NCIS Special Agent Afloat on the USS Van Buren.
昨日被发现死亡
He was discovered dead yesterday.
死因是钝器重击头部
Cause of death was blunt force trauma,
可能是坠落或是故意的棒击
either from a fall or a deliberate bludgeoning.
- 有目击者吗  - 没
- Any witnesses?  - No.
嫌疑人呢
Suspects?
可能有一个
Possibly one.
Simon Allen士官是个情报专家
Petty Officer Simon Allen is an intelligence specialist.
根据Niles探员最后的报告
Now, according to Agent Niles's last report,
他正因"行为古怪"监视着Allen士官
he was keeping an eye on Petty Officer Allen for "Erratic behavior."
那什么意思
What does that mean?
他日志里没详细说明 但Allen士官现在被关禁闭
Well, he doesn't specify in his log but Petty Officer Allen is currently in the brig
因与海军陆战队上士发生争执
following an altercation with a Marine staff sergeant
尸体也是在当天早晨被人发现的
on the same morning that the body was found.
他们为啥争执
What were they fighting about?
不知道
Not sure.
但两人可卡因检查都呈阳性
But both men tested positive for cocaine use.
范布伦号现在在哪
Where's the Van Buren now?
正去日本海 让朝鲜老实点
It's on its way to the Sea of Japan to keep North Korea in line.
那我们应该干什么
So then, what are we supposed to do?
你们最擅长的
What you do best.
解决罪案
Solve the crime.
我已经安排好你们所有人飞去航母
I've already arranged for you all to be flown out to the ship.
圣诞节得等等了
Christmas is going to have to wait.
哇
Wow.
你好啊 水手
Hello, sailor.
我是海军陆战队少校
I'm a Marine major.
你是个少校辣妹
You're a major hotty.
这服装好带劲啊
Oh. Those are some cool costumes.
是军服 它们不是一般的服装 Deeks
Uniform. They're not costumes, Deeks.
我们卧底成船员 Callen装成NCIS海上特别探员的替补
We're going in as crew members, and Callen's going in as the replacement for the NCIS Agent Afloat.
嗯 那我的卧底是啥
Mm-hmm. So what's my cover?
你嘛 小弟弟
You, my friend,
装成给电脑升级的平民承包商
are a civilian contractor doing a computer upgrade.
一个计算机宅
A geek?
我就这装备吗 剪贴板
This is all I get? This, like, clipboard?
航母上有5千多人
There are over 5,000 people on board.
卧底成不同的船员能让我们查的更广
Going in as different elements of the crew will allow us to cover more ground.
顺便说一声 这明显是对我卧底才能的滥用
Mm-hmm. Just for the record, this is a gross misuse of my undercover talents.
如果你真这么想 Deeks先生
Well, if you truly feel that way, Mr. Deeks,
你也可以卧底成海军陆战队
you can go in as a Marine, as well.
让我去先拿下剪刀  - 啥
- Just let me get my clippers.  - What?
剪刀
Clippers?
你要剃个小光头肯定酷毙了
Ooh, you're gonna look so good with a high and tight.
别别别 等等
No, no. No, no, no, no, wait.
我正在做一些
Just got to do a little, uh,
卧底人物的记忆工作
sense memory work for my undercover character, you know.
红皮革 黄皮革 红皮革 黄皮革
Red leather, yellow leather. Red leather, yellow leather.
开演 哈
Acting, ha!
直升机带我们去科罗纳多号
Chopper's here to take us to Coronado.
我知道这表情
I know that look.
你越来越像我老婆了
You're starting to sound like my wife.
你知道他们怎么说 当你搭档像你老婆时吗
You know what they say when your partner starts sounding like your wife?
换个老婆吗
Get a new wife?
我要装作没听到
I'm gonna pretend you didn't say that.
看到没 这就是问题所在
See, that's the problem right there.
我们俩都不怎么聊了
You and I don't talk.
少了交流 关系也很快就淡了
Communication goes, the relationship is soon to follow.
说完了吗
Almost finished?
快了
Just about.
听着 我知道你想在家过圣诞节
Look, I know you want to be home for Christmas.
我都错过了圣诞节 毕业典礼 生日
I've missed Christmas, graduations, birthdays
还有其他一切
and everything else doing what we do.
那是什么原因
Then what is it?
Sidirov
Sidirov.
如果他趁我们不在时回来了咋办
What if he comes back while we're away?
Michelle会做她该做的
Then Michelle will do what she has to do.
就和你在这一样
Same is if you were here.
没错 但我不在
Yeah. But I won't be.
那我们就速度点
Then we'll make this quick.
还有 我向你保证
Besides, I guarantee you,
Sidirov近期不会来这
Sidirov isn't showing up here anytime soon.
你怎么能确定呢
How can you be so sure?
罪犯也和我们一样圣诞节要放假
Criminals take Christmas off just like the rest of us.
坏人们也不想出现在淘气鬼名单上
Even the bad guys don't like being on the naughty list.
海军有着1550亿的预算
The Navy has a budget of $155 billion,
却开这种飞机
and this is the plane that they use?
C2灰狗运输机 海中驮马
C2 Greyhound-- workhorse of the sea.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
好吧 这马儿得淘汰了（glue factory 收养老马的地方）
Yeah, well, this horse needs to be sent to the glue factory.
这或许是你做过的最安全的飞机了
It's probably the safest plane you'll ever fly in.
这安全 搞笑了
Th-This is the safe... Really?
解释给我听听 为嘛我们还得戴着头盔
Okay, explain to me, then, why we're wearing helmets
还要穿救生衣
and life preservers.
错了就纠正我 是要在水上迫降
Correct me if I'm wrong, but the only time
才要穿救生衣的
to wear a life preserver is in the event of a water landing.
跟我说说 你知道什么内幕消息
So tell me, do they know something that we don't know?
没什么好怕的 Deeks
There is nothing to be afraid of, Deeks.
什么 我才不怕 我有着钢铁般的意志
What? I'm not. I have hardened nerves of steel.
我只是感到有些不安
I just think it's a little disconcerting
者飞机后边开得跟我家的车库一样大
the back of the plane opens like my garage door.
就像是会飞的工具房
It's like a flying tool shed.
- Deeks - 怎么
- Deeks? - Yeah?
我在睡觉呢
I'm trying to sleep here.
好吧 飞机要是坠落到海里
Okay. Well, I'll be sure to wake you up
我会叫醒你的
when we crash into the ocean.
放松点 牛仔
Hey, just try and relax, Maverick.
啊 你听到了吗
Huh? Did you hear that?
怎么感觉有点像壮志凌云的感觉
I look a little Top Gun in this thing, don't I?
我收集前几个月的一大堆训练报告
Hey, I gathered a bunch of disciplinary reports from the last several months.
找找看有谁跟特别探员Niles有冲突
Trying to find anyone who might have a grudge against Special Agent Niles.
听起来不错
That sounds good.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事 好着呢
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Nell
Nell?
Nellie
Nellie?
小Nell
Nellster...
我很期待这秘密的圣诞聚会
It's just... I was really looking forward to the holiday party and the Secret Santa stuff.
我好傻
It's... it's stupid.
我可不这么看
I don't think so.
我很期待这假期
I'm so... I just get like this around the holidays.
因为回不了家
'Cause I... I can't be home.
还有我的同事们
And it's like these people we work with,
他们成了我们的家人代替 可他们现在人都不在这
they become...our surrogate family, and they're not here right now.
他们会很快回来
They'll be back soon.
这么着吧 他们要是不回来
And you know what, even if they're not,
我保证我们还是会有节日庆祝的
I promise that we will have a festive holiday celebration.
我是说我会戴上精灵帽子
I mean, I've agreed to wear an elf hat,
还有着耳朵
so... And the ears?
说什么 还有啥
I'm sorry, the what?
你还得戴上这精灵耳朵
You have to wear the elf ears.
我记得我没说过要戴着玩意
Um, I don't think I remember you saying anything about any...
摆脱啦
Oh, come on.
哪有精灵没耳朵的
Hey, what's an elf without ears, right?
对了
Exactly.
准备降落
Prepare for landing.
无压力 就不知你们担心个啥来着
Piece of cake! I don't know what you guys were so worried about.
欢迎来到范布伦号 女士 长官
Welcome aboard the USS Van Buren, ma'am, sirs.
我是Smalls士官
I'm Petty Officer Smalls.
要我为你指引方向吗 中校
Can I point you in the right direction, Commander?
不用 我没事 特别探员Callen
No, I'm good, thanks. Special Agent Callen,
要带你到NCIS的办公室吗
would you like to be taken to the NCIS office?
我先去警卫室
Actually, I'm headed to the brig first,
但我找不到了路 谢啦
but can find my way. Thanks.
你肯是Colter先生
You must be Mr. Colter,
数据访问分析师
the data entry systems analyst.
你说成dayta 我说data
Well, you say "Day-ta," I say data--
我看咱们就统一叫成data
I say we split the difference and call it a date.
我是文职人员联络官
I'm the ship's civilian personnel liaison.
我是你的随从
I'll be your escort.
马上就有人接待你的 女士
Someone should be here to meet you momentarily, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
好极啦
Fantastic.
我不知道你有没有听说过
I don't know if you, uh, overheard that,
我有着随从
but I have a, uh, escort.
在舰上是不允许亲密接触的 Deeks
Fraternization is forbidden on board, Deeks.
这么大的醋味
Wow, jealous much?
Barret少校
Major Barret?
不好意思 来晚了
Please excuse my tardiness, ma'am.
我是Abernathy上尉
I'm Lieutenant Abernathy.
欢迎
Welcome aboard.
谢谢 上尉
Thank you, Lieutenant.
跟我来 我带你到你的住宿点
If you'll follow me, I'll show you to your berthing.
You can get squared away before you muster on station. Yes.
So what, they found the missing link.
Are you coming, Mr. Colter?
Oh. Colter, no. Please call me Marty.
And I should call you...?
Petty Officer Smalls will suffice, sir.
All right.
So, what were you and Staff Sergeant Jefferies fighting about?
I don't know, sir. It was stupid.
I mean, you know what the Marines are like.
"Oorah" This and "Oorah" That.
Sometimes it just gets a little tiresome
and you have to stand up to them
or else they walk around like they own the place.
You two have a history?
Absolutely not, sir.
I couldn't pick him out of a lineup.
He and his boys were lipping off,
so I told them to shut it.
Next think you know, he's tackling me.
Guess he figured he had something to prove.
Did this fight have anything to do with cocaine?
I can't speak for Petty Officer Allen,
but I did not, nor have I ever used cocaine.
Then how do you explain your drug test?
It must be a mistake, sir.
I'd gladly be retested.
Oh, so you test negative now that it's out of your system?
It was never in my system, sir.
I'm no angel, Agent Callen,
but I'll take a lie detector to prove I'm no drug user.
My father and my uncle were Marines.
I would never disrespect this uniform,
this ship or my family by doing something so stupid.
What's your relationship with the NCIS Special Agent Afloat
Jason Niles?
I never even knew
who he was until I heard he was reported dead.
Yeah, I-I only met him once.
He intervened in an argument I was having a few days ago.
What was the argument about?
It was music. Some E3 was in the library
listening to music with his headphones,
but he had the tunes cranked so loud, it was bugging everybody.
Where were you yesterday
prior to the... altercation in the galley?
Fire safety drills.
I had the morning watch.
Which ends at 8:00? Yes, sir.
The fight took place just after 9:00,
so what were you doing for the hour in-between?
Uh, usually I would jog around the deck,
but flight operations were in full swing,
so I just walked below deck.
Uh-huh. Why didn't you use the treadmills in the gym?
I always feel like a hamster on those things, sir.
Anyone see you?
Uh, yeah, sure, lots of people.
Anyone see you around the... zero-two-tack-
one-eight-two-tack- six-tango section of the ship?
I-I can't be sure, sir.
Where exactly is that?
Where the body was found.
The bull's-eyes tell you where you are
Deck, frame, relation to centerline and compartment.
Numbers increase as you go aft.
Even numbers are port, odd numbers are starboard.
Starbucks? S-Starboard.
No, I mean, is there a Starbucks on board?
Or a Coffee Bean?
Panda Express? T.G.I. Fridays?
Froyo?
Enlisted Mess is
on the second level.
The Dirty Shirt Room, Wardroom One, is forward
on the O3 level.
Chief's Mess has the best food,
but you have to be invited.
If you'll follow me this way, Mr. Colter...
Mr. Colter? Hello?
What's up there, sailors?
Nothing to see here.
What the... what?
What the hell are you doing? Me? No. I was just...
I was just looking for the bathroom.
I got lost coming around one of these corners.
I found myself in the basement of the Titanic.
Seriously, I think I just saw Kate Winslet.
She was naked. You should check it... out.
Hey, I see how this is--
you guys, uh, want to haze the swabbie.
Here's the problem--
I'm a private contractor, which means you can't
dress me up like a sea hag, or whatever it is
you and your seaman buddy here do for fun.
What the hell is going on in here?
He was creeping around where we found that NCIS agent dead, sir.
Sir, you know what they say about criminals,
always returning to the scene of the crime.
Yeah, except for Matlock,
I'm pretty sure no one actually says that.
I'll take him from here.
They're gone.
I just need... Come on, Deeks,
pull your skirt down-- I hardly hit you.
I know, I was... I was just in character.
It's fine. I'm fine.
You've been on the ship less than an hour,
and you're already in trouble. Yeah, I know,
but I found evidence.
Special Agent Niles
was killed on a different part of the ship,
and then his body was dragged here.
These are the sailors who attacked Deeks.
Both men have had minor incidents while on shore leave,